<?xml version="1.0" standalone='yes' ?>
	<pages>	
		<backgroundImages>
				<image>
					<src>images/site/backgrounds/hana-background-2.jpg</src>
					<caption><![CDATA[<p>Something happens when you meditate outside by the ocean.</p>]]></caption>
				</image>
				<image>
					<src>images/site/backgrounds/hana-background-4.jpg</src>
					<caption><![CDATA[<p>Sunrise Yoga with stunning ocean views and warm breezes.</p>]]></caption>
				</image>

		</backgroundImages>
		<elopement>
			<secondaryPages>
				<page section="0" parentId="0" secondaryNav="true" id="0" position="1"  sitemapId="3.0" sitemapTitle="Elopement">
					<title>Hana Elopement Package</title>
					<meta>
						<slug>elopement</slug>
						<pageTitle>Hana Elopement Package</pageTitle>
						<description>Travaasa Hana Elopement Package</description>
						<keywords>travaasa, elopement, package, magazine, hawaii, Hana, hotel, resort, maui, weddin</keywords>
					</meta>
					<h1><![CDATA[Hana Elopement Package]]></h1>
					<copy><![CDATA[
					
					<div class="gray-box">
						<h3>Weddings in Paradise</h3>

						<p>Nestled between the Haleakala mountain range and the Pacific
						ocean on the east coast of Maui, lays a tropical oasis called
						Hana. In ancient Hawaiian legend Hana is where the island of
						Maui was pulled out of the ocean and born into the Hawaiian
						island chain.</p>

						<p>So too shall your new life together be born - in the exact same
						spot. Surrounded by mystery and beauty, historic Hana town
						exudes a blend of aloha spirit and country charm.</p>

						<p>The journey to Hana begins when your plane touches down on
						the island of Maui. Your senses will be overtaken by the smell of
						Tuberose, Pikake and Plumeria flowers that abound year-round
						throughout the island.</p>

						<p>As the singing of little birds welcome you and the warm Pacific
						tradewinds envelop your being, you will rejoice because you have
						just stepped into the land of Aloha.</p>

						<p>When you arrive at the Travaasa Hana our well trained sta will welcome you with
						open arms. They live the Aloha spirit. E komo mai. Come and stay where authentic
						Hawaiian traditions are still a way of life. Learn how to Hula dance, string a flower lei
						or play the Ukulele.</p>

						<p>We will take care of all the details so you can make a vacation out of your wedding. Pamper
						yourself at our award winning Spa. Pla y a game of tennis, go for a bike ride or hike to
						the 300 foot Waimoku waterfall. Relax at our infinity pool, whale watch from the water’s
						edge at the world famous Hamoa Beach, or just lay in the hammock and read a book.
						An intimate wedding for up to four people on the black lava rock blu at the Pacific’s edge
						awaits you. Your vision of an island wedding is a dream come true when you get married at
						our Sea Ranch Resort. And, with the devoted sta of the Travaasa Hana on your team,
						you can dream away...</p>

						<h3>Elopement Wedding $5,000</h3>

						<ul>
						<li>Two-night Stay in our Deluxe OceanView Sea Ranch Cottage with Private Hot Tub</li>
						<li>Deluxe Welcome Amenity Basket upon Arrival</li>
						<li>Bottle of Champagne Upon Arrival</li>
						<li>Personal Services of our Travaasa Hana Wedding Specialist</li>
						<li>Arrangement of the Marriage License Appointment</li>
						<li>Non-denominational Officiant to Preside over Ceremony</li>
						<li>Choice of Traditional Hawaiian Wedding Lei or Bridal Bouquet for Bride</li>
						<li>Choice of Boutonnière or Traditional Hawaiian Wedding Lei for Groom</li>
						<li>500 CT Orchid Flower Scatter at Ceremony Site</li>
						<li>Special Wedding Gift from Travaasa Hana</li>
						<li>Steaming of Bride’s and Groom’s Wedding Attire</li>
						<li>Private Transportation To and From Ceremony Site for Bride and Groom</li>
						<li>Witness if Needed</li>
						<li>Daily Breakfast, Lunch and Dinner for Two Included</li>
						<li>Orchid Flowers Scattered in Room Upon Return from Ceremony or Reception</li>
						<li>Choice of One Premium Activity such as Horseback Riding, etc. </li>
						<li>During You Stay Daily Spa Treatment for Two</li>
						</ul>
					</div>
					]]></copy>
					<thumbImg>images/site/natural-beauty-crisman-t.jpg</thumbImg>
					<thumbCaption>Travaasa Hana Elopement Package</thumbCaption>
					<mainImg>images/site/hana-libations.jpg</mainImg>
					<imageCaption></imageCaption>
					<Storybook></Storybook>
					<pdf_downloads>
						<pdf>
							<title></title>
							<url></url>
						</pdf>
					</pdf_downloads>
				</page>				
			</secondaryPages>
		</elopement>
	</pages>
