<?xml version="1.0" standalone='yes' ?>
	<pages>	
		<backgroundImages>
				<image>
					<src>images/site/backgrounds/hana-background-2.jpg</src>
					<caption><![CDATA[<p>Something happens when you meditate outside by the ocean.</p>]]></caption>
				</image>
				<image>
					<src>images/site/backgrounds/hana-background-4.jpg</src>
					<caption><![CDATA[<p>Sunrise Yoga with stunning ocean views and warm breezes.</p>]]></caption>
				</image>

		</backgroundImages>
		<elopement>
			<secondaryPages>
				<page section="0" parentId="0" secondaryNav="true" id="0" position="1"  sitemapId="3.0" sitemapTitle="Elopement">
					<title>Hana Elopement Package</title>
					<meta>
						<slug>elopement</slug>
						<pageTitle>Hana Elopement Package</pageTitle>
						<description>Travaasa Hana Elopement Package</description>
						<keywords>travaasa, elopement, package, magazine, hawaii, Hana, hotel, resort, maui, weddin</keywords>
					</meta>
					<h1><![CDATA[Hana Elopement Package]]></h1>
					<copy><![CDATA[
					
					<div class="gray-box">
						<h2>Weddings in Paradise</h2>

						<p>Nestled between the Haleakala mountain range and the Pacific Ocean, the tropical oasis of Hana on the east coast of Maui awaits. In ancient Hawaiian legend from Hana, Maui was pulled out of the ocean and born into the Hawaiian island chain. Your new life together begins in the exact same spot. Surrounded by mystery and beauty, historic Hana town exudes a blend of aloha spirit and small town charm.</p>

						<p>The journey to Hana begins the second your plane lands. Your senses are overtaken by the sweet scent of tuberose, pikake and plumeria flowers. As the singing of little birds welcome you and the warm Pacific trade winds envelop your being, rejoice as you step into the land of Aloha.</p>

						<p>Our well-trained and dedicated staff invites you to stay where authentic Hawaiian traditions are a way of life. Try throw net fishing, learn how to dance hula, string a fresh ti-leaf lei, or play the ukulele. Then pamper yourself in our award-winning spa, go for a bike ride, hike to the 400-foot Waimoku Falls, relax at our infinity pool, frolick at the world-famous Hamoa Beach, or just lay in a hammock and read a book.</p> 

						<p>An intimate wedding for up to four people on black lava rock at the Pacific’s edge awaits you. Your vision of an island wedding is a dream come true at our sea ranch resort. Dream away…</p>
						
						<h2>Elopement Wedding $5,000</h2>
						<ul>
						<li>Two-night Stay in our Deluxe Ocean View Sea Ranch Cottage with Private Hot Tub</li>
						<li>Deluxe Welcome Amenity Basket upon Arrival</li>
						<li>Bottle of Champagne Upon Arrival</li>
						<li>Personal Services of our Travaasa Hana Wedding Specialist</li>
						<li>Arrangement of the Marriage License Appointment</li>
						<li>Non-Denominational Officiant to Preside over Ceremony</li>
						<li>Choice of Traditional Hawaiian Wedding Lei or Bridal Bouquet for Bride</li>
						<li>Choice of Boutonnière or Traditional Hawaiian Wedding Lei for Groom</li>
						<li>500 CT Orchid Flower Scatter at Ceremony Site</li>
						<li>Special Wedding Gift from Travaasa Hana</li>
						<li>Steaming of Bride’s and Groom’s Wedding Attire</li>
						<li>Private Transportation To and From Ceremony Site for Bride and Groom</li>
						<li>Witness if Needed</li>
						<li>Daily Breakfast, Lunch and Dinner for Two Included</li>
						<li>Orchid Flowers Scattered in Room Upon Return from Ceremony or Reception</li>
						<li>Choice of One Premium Activity such as Coastal Horseback Ride, Adventure Glider Ride, etc.</li>
						<li>Daily Spa Treatment for Two</li>
						</ul>
					</div>
					]]></copy>
					<thumbImg>images/site/natural-beauty-crisman-t.jpg</thumbImg>
					<thumbCaption>Travaasa Hana Elopement Package</thumbCaption>
					<mainImg>images/site/hana-libations.jpg</mainImg>
					<imageCaption></imageCaption>
					<Storybook></Storybook>
					<pdf_downloads>
						<pdf>
							<title></title>
							<url></url>
						</pdf>
					</pdf_downloads>
				</page>				
			</secondaryPages>
		</elopement>
	</pages>
